shareadult.com 2015-12-23

# 

Complete our simple verification to gain instant access.

Featuring real amateurs pics and vids!

### PRIVACY

We (Deluxe Productions Ltd) are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

## Information Collection and Use

We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points throughout our Site.

## Registration Form

To become a member of our Site, a user must complete the on-line registration form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include your full name, mailing address, and e-mail address). This information is used to set-up and maintain an account, verify credit card details, validate credit identity. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

## Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use an outside company or companies to process payments or to fulfill orders and consequently we may need to pass on personal information about you in order for your payment to be processed. From time to time, we may contract with another party to provide certain specific services to our users. If we have collected your personally identifiable information from one site, that site may share the information with another site within our network in order to provide you with additional goods and services for which we believe you may be interested and by visiting the Site you are hereby deemed to have consented to us doing this.

## Law Enforcement

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child pornography.

## Links

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Security

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures.

## Third Party Sources of Information

From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive from you with information we obtain from third party sources.

## Children

Our Site is not intended for children. Our Site does not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit.

## Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, he/she may contact us to correct or update this information.

## Choice/Opt-out

From time to time, we may send our users e-mails or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us.

## UK Data Protection Act 1998

We are committed to protecting the rights and privacy of individuals in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. We process information about staff, customers and other individuals we have dealings with for a range of administrative purposes (e.g. to recruit and pay staff, deliver services and comply with legal obligations to government). In order to comply with the law, information about individuals must be collected and used fairly, stored safely and securely and not disclosed to any third party unlawfully. All "processing" of personal data (includes collection, holding, retention, destruction and use of personal data) are governed by the Data Protection Act 1998. The Act applies to all personal data - whether they are held on a computer or similar automatic system or whether they are held as part of a manual file. Personal data is defined as information relating to an identifiable living individual and can be held in any format, electronic (including websites and emails), paper-based, photographic etc. from which the individual's information can be readily extracted. Under the 1998 Act, all organisations that process personal information are required to notify the Information Commissioner's Office.

## Visitors from outside of the United Kingdom

All matters relating to the Site are governed by the laws of England and Wales and are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. Any information you provide will be transferred to the United Kingdom. By visiting our Site and submitting information, you authorize this transfer.

Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use our Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending a message. Please provide us with your password, username and account number so we can service you quicker.

Contact us [here](http://wwww.supportdeluxe.com/) and one of our Customer Support people will be happy to reply to your request. A response will be forwarded to your Email address within a reasonable period.
